{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
老佛爷lfy\h\h\hKathie228\h\h\h\h莲花葬在深海\h\h\h\hBlack丶
Orun!que\h\h\h汤包小螺螺\h\h\h\h-Satellite
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
Junosis\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
手抬起来  手抬起来
Keep your hands up, keep your hands up.
♪ 当你看着我时  你又怎么知道 ♪
♪ How could you ever know When you look at me ♪
♪ 我经历了一个世纪的挑战 ♪
♪ That I've been through enough Challenge for a century? ♪
♪ 身体上和精神上都有 ♪
♪ Both physically And mentally ♪
♪ 麻烦会跟上我 ♪
♪ This shit will catch up with me ♪
♪ 把我绑起  最后让我 ♪
♪ Pin me down and render me ♪
♪ 丧失能力 ♪
♪ Incapacitated eventually ♪
♪ 我讨厌这会是我的末日 ♪
♪ I hate it It'll be the end of me ♪
♪ 不是可能  而是一定的 ♪
♪ And this is for certain This is not potentially ♪
♪ 这是致命的  我的精神不断崩溃 ♪
♪ It's deadly, the way I'm Breaking down so steadily ♪
♪ 虽然你看到我在笑  听到我在开玩笑 ♪
♪ Though you see me smiling Though you hear me jokin'♪
♪ 虽然我在一直闪耀  你会 ♪
♪ Though I keep shining You would--♪
嗨  卡姆拉
Hi Kamura.
你在桌子上干什么
What are you doing on the table?
你不该上桌子
You're not supposed to be on the table.
♪ 我只是在坚持 ♪
♪ I'm just hanging on Hanging on ♪
♪ 从黑夜  从黑夜 ♪
♪ Through the night Through the night ♪
♪ 直到黎明  直到黎明 ♪
♪ To the dawn To the dawn ♪
♪ 我只是试着去  试着去 ♪
♪ And I'm just tryna make it Tryna make it ♪
♪ 再熬过一夜  再过一夜 ♪
♪ One more night One more night ♪
♪ 我看到了光 ♪
♪ I see the light ♪
布娃娃
♪ 他们说杀不死你的只会让你变强 ♪
♪ They say what doesn't Kill you only makes you strong ♪
♪ 他们想的太简单  他们弄错了 ♪
♪ They had it easy They got it wrong ♪
♪ 如果它让你崩溃直到部分的你消失 ♪
♪ What if it breaks you down 'Til a piece of you is gone ♪
♪ 我无法再前进 ♪
♪ I'll never move on ♪
♪ 我已经被改变了  我将不再是原来的我 ♪
♪ I've been changed in a way That I'll never be the same ♪
♪ 我每天都祈祷能让我度过这痛苦 ♪
♪ I pray every day just to get Me through this pain ♪
♪ 我试着挺起来  试着振作起来 ♪
♪ I try to lift me up I try to pick me up ♪
♪ 我经历了这一切  但我从未放弃 ♪
♪ I been through it all but I Ain't never giving up ♪
♪ 我只是在坚持 ♪
♪ I'm just hanging on Hanging on ♪
♪ 从黑夜  从黑夜 ♪
♪ Through the night Through the night ♪
♪ 直到黎明  直到黎明 ♪
♪ To the dawn To the dawn ♪
♪ 我只是试着去  试着去 ♪
♪ And I'm just tryna make it Tryna make it ♪
♪ 再熬过一夜  再过一夜 ♪
♪ One more night One more night ♪
♪ 我看到了光 ♪
♪ I see the light ♪
妈  你吓死我了
Mom, you scared the shit out of me.
我还以为有人闯进了房子
I thought somebody had broken into the house!
你一大早在干什么
What are you doing up so early?
今天看起来是看日出的好日子
Today just seemed like the perfect day to see the sunrise.
我可能把床弄脏了  也可能没有
Oh, and I may or may not have shat the bed.
先来把你洗干净
Let's get you cleaned up.
妈妈
Mom?
-嘿  -怎么
- Hey. - Yeah?
我只是告诉你彼得斯太太来了
Hey, I just wanted to let you know Mrs. Peters is here.
彼得斯  她来干什么
Mrs. Peters, what the hell for?
今天你休息  诺拉
It's your day off, Nora.
今天是他妈的星期天
It's fucking Sunday.
我可能失去了很多  但我还没失去理智
I may be losing a lot of things, but my mind is not one of them.
是的  你很有理智  妈妈
Yes, you are of very sound mind, Mom.
那当然
That's right.
你感觉还好吗
Are you feeling alright?
好  我很好
Yeah, I'm great.
我要去训练馆了  好吗
Well, I'm gonna take off to the gym, okay?
好吧
Alright.
我一会儿回来
I'll be back later.
你自便
Knock yourself out.
今天对彼得斯太太好点  好吗
Be nice to Mrs. Peters today, okay?
不  不可能
No. I won't.
我买了牛奶  昨天就用完了
I bought milk. You ran out yesterday.
对不起  我没想到
I'm sorry, I didn't think about it.
我泡茶需要牛奶
I need milk for my tea.
我答应照看房子的时候就告诉过你的
I told you that when I agreed to watch over the house.
对不起  我会做得更好的
I'm sorry, I'll do better.
请务必做到
Please see that you do.
我要求很少了
I ask so little.
最后的幸存女
都缠在一起了
It's all knotted up.
加油  姑娘  继续呼吸
Come on girl, keep breathing.
呼吸  行了  你们来吧
Breathe through it! Alright, you guys do it.
孩子  你里面很僵硬
You got like a sack of marbles in there, kid.
你晚上有拉伸吗
You stretchin' at night?
你撒谎  你他妈的都答不对
You liar. You can't even fucking answer me right.
好吧  我的布娃娃呢
Alright, where's my rag doll?
诺拉  去吧  你得给阿依莎热身  去吧
Come on Nora, let's go, you gotta warm up Aisha. Let's go!
你被锁住了  要窒息了
Let's go. You're on her. Get that choke out.
你打算怎么办  快啊
What are you gonna do? Come on!
好了
There you go.
现在如果她想过去你怎么办
Now what are you gonna do if she tries to pass through?
对  把胳膊收回去
Yeah, take the arm back!
听着  你甚至不需要用手
Look, you don't even need to use your hands!
侧向压制
Side control!
来吧  姑娘  试下
Come on girl, take that.
去锁臂
Get the arm bar!
好的  锁牢了
Alright, arm bars all day!
事实上  我可以挣脱
Well actually, I can transition out of this.
诺拉  停  注意膝盖  快啊
Hey Nora, stop, watch the knee, come on!
对不起
Sorry.
嘿  停下来
Hey, shake it off.
好吧  我们  闹够了
Alright, well, let's... well that's enough of this shit.
我们换个项目吧  阿依莎  走吧
Let's move on to something else. Aisha, come on. Let's go.
请给我另找个人
Find me someone else please.
你  过来
Hey! Yeah you. Come on.
干得不错
Hey, good job.
我喜欢这样的
I like what I'm seeing.
谢谢
Thanks.
这儿  这儿  这儿  这儿
Here, here, here. Here.
水
Water.
这儿  这儿
Here, here.
过来
Come here.
冷静  冷静
Calm down, calm down.
我在这里  妈妈  没事的
I'm here, I'm here Mama. It's okay.
我会一直在这里
I'm always gonna be here.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom, hey.
我得去上班了  你感觉好些了吗
I gotta take off to work. Are you feeling better?
真他妈
Fuckin' A.
妈  别说脏话  认真的
Mom, language, seriously.
我以为我们谈的是积极的方面
I thought we talked about the positivity thing.
只是语言而已  诺拉
They're only words, Nora.
就像穿过73号  空挡反击
Like 73 across. The blank strikes back.
研究表明积极乐观不自怨自艾
Positive energy and no cursing,
会帮助你清除很多消极情绪
research says is gonna help you clear out a lot of negativity.
考虑到我的坏影响
Given all my bad influence,
你怎么会变成女童子军的
how'd you end up such a Girl Scout?
还他妈是真的
That's fucking true.
一点也不好笑
You're not funny.
你他妈的玩得很开心
You have a fucking good time.
今晚见
I'll see you tonight.
谢谢
Thanks.
我能帮你什么忙吗
How can I help you?
我电话订购了我妈妈的处方
I called in an order to fill in my mom's prescription.
凯瑟琳·坡名下
It's under Catherine Poe.
凯瑟琳·坡
Catherine Poe?
你是凯瑟琳·坡吗
And you're Catherine Poe?
不  那是我妈妈
Uh, no, that's my mother.
-你不是凯瑟琳·坡吗  -不是
- You're not Catherine Poe? - No.
等等
Hold on.
她名字在这里  但是
She's in here, but...
我的系统报错了  说不能再补充了
There's an error in my system, says no refills.
我可以再给你补充一次  但只此一次
I can give you another refill but just as a one-time courtesy.
可以吗
Okay?
可以
Mhmm. Okay.
-什么  -谢谢
- What? - Thank you.
那要七十美元
That will be seventy dollars.
不是吧
Oh, no.
事实上  我妈妈有医保所以不应该收费
Actually, my mom has Medicare so that shouldn't be any cost.
好的
Okay.
上面说这种药的分类已经改变了
So it says here the classification for this drug has changed.
医疗保险只报销75%  剩下的是你自费
Medicare only covers seventy-five percent. The rest is your copay.
所以  自费70美元
So then the copay is the seventy dollars.
自费70美元
The co-pay is the seventy dollars.
我没有七十美元
Well, I don't have seventy dollars.
你有信用卡吗
Do you have a credit card?
没
No.
-借记卡  -不  我没有
- Debit card? - No, I don't have...
我们不收支票
We don't take checks.
不  听着  你不明白  我没有七十美元
No, listen, you don't understand. I don't have seventy dollars.
一直是免费的
This has always been free.
我没被人通知或者什么的
You know I was never called about this or anything,
所以我今天没准备付钱  我没有七十美元
so I wasn't prepared to pay today, so I don't have seventy dollars.
我不知道你想让我怎么做
I don't know what you want me to do, um...
I don't know what you want me to do.
听着  药物的分类已经改变了
Look, the classification for the drug has changed.
我真的没有办法帮你
There's really nothing I can do.
你知道那药是什么吗
Do you know what that medication is?
你知道那是什么吗  我需要它做什么吗
You know what the-- what that does? What I need it for?
你知道我妈妈需要那种药  否则她会死的
You're aware that my mom needs that medication, or she could die.
你知道的  对吧
Like you're aware of that, right?
这一直是免费的  所以我觉得
This has always been free. So I think there's just...
我认为你搞错了  你得纠正它
I think you're doing something incorrect, and you need to fix it.
好吗  我从来没有付过钱
Okay. I've never had to pay for this.
你觉得我弄错了
You think I'm incorrect?
是的  我觉得你应该看看你的电脑
Yes, I do. I think you should look into your computer
想办法给我妈弄到这些药
and figure out a way to get my mother these drugs!
给你妈妈这些药的方法是给我七十美元
The way to get your mom these drugs is to give me seventy dollars.
这他妈的胡扯  你能去找别人吗
This is fucking bullshit, can you go get somebody?
医生  医生  可以谈谈吗
Hey, hey doc. Hey doc, can I?
去找你的经理  我得去上班了
Go get your manager. I gotta go to work.
所以我他妈的得离开这里
So I need to fucking get outta here
医生  我能
Doc, can I?
拜托  能给我妈妈的药吗
So please, can you give me my mom's medication.
药剂师  我能和你谈一下吗
Pharmacist? Can I talk to you for a second?
等一下  好的  等一下
One second. Yeah, hold on.
如果可以的话我来买单
So I'll just take care of it if it's okay.
什么
What?
可以的话我来买单
I'll just take care of it if it's okay.
我们可以把它算到我的东西里  我们买单
We can just add it to my, to my stuff and we can handle it.
什么  这不是酒吧  先生  你在说什么
What? This isn't a bar ,sir. What-- what are you saying?
我会为她的东西买单
I'll just take care of her stuff.
-她的东西  -是啊
- Her stuff? - Yeah!
你想帮这个女人付钱吗
You want to pay for this woman?
-是啊  -不  我不能让你这么做
- Yeah. - Oh, no, I can't let you do that.
不  没问题  说真的  没什么大不了的
No, it's no problem. Seriously, it's not a big deal.
不  真的
No, like really.
-不  我   -听着  我没钱还你
- No, I... - Look, I don't have money to pay you back.
随便你  我只是
Look it's up to you, I just...
我姐姐得了癌症  所以我明白你的遭遇
My sister had cancer, so I understand what you're going through...
还有  我明白
and uh, yeah, I mean, I got it--
你是个好人
You're a nice man.
杰森·赖特  姓里有个"W"
Jason Wright. With a "W".
With a "W". Wright.
-对  -对
- Right. - Right.
好  依地普仑  利培酮
Okay. Lexapro, Risperdal...
对
Yeah! Yes.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
还早呢  我要喝咖啡
It's early. I need some coffee.
你要咖啡吗  想来点咖啡吗
You need some coffee? Wanna get some coffee?
马上就好
There's instant.
你可以取了
You can just have it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祝你今天顺心愉快
Have a good day. Have a better day. Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们点的饮品  请在这取
I have your drinks right here.
我来付  不要和我客气
Yo, I got this. Don't even mess with me.
随你
Okay.
一共是11.5美元
That'll be $11.50.
该死
Shit.
你是说  你的姐姐患了癌症吗
So um... you said your-- your sister had cancer?
对  乳腺癌
Yeah. Breast.
那你们是怎么应对的呢
Oh. What did you guys do?
你们是直接去化疗了吗
Did you guys just do like straight chemo?
还是去尝试了  新的药物测试什么的
Did you try, like, the new drug trials, or...
医生之前一直误诊
The doctors kept misdiagnosing her.
所以当他们查清我姐姐的病的时候
I mean, like, when they found out what it actually was,
已经是晚期了
it was too late.
我很抱歉
I'm...I'm so sorry.
没事  死亡就是  死亡
Oh yeah, no. I mean, death is... death.
但是  你不能倒退  不是吗
But you can't-- you can't go backwards, right?
你不能回到以前
You can't go backwards.
我猜
That's what all this--
这就是那些精神药物的
I mean, I guess what some of these
用处了
head drugs are for,
我会去参加一些组织  聚会谈心
and I talk to the group. I go-- I go to this group.
非常有意思  有超酷的猫
Very cool group meeting, super cool cats,
我们还会一起看电影  看书什么的
and we-- we watch movies and we read these books, and um.
听着  我知道你
Yo, you know, I know you're probably also
也正在经历一些  难过的关
goin' through some, some heavy stuff,
所以我很想让你认识一下派特
and I could totally introduce you to Pat.
派特  她是这个组织的头头
Pat, she's my-- she's the group leader
而且她酷毙了
and she's a super cool chick.
谢谢你  但不用了
No, I'm good. Thank you, though, yeah.
-你不想吗  -这
- Yeah? Right. - That's not--
不是  你误会我了  我只是
No, I mean, no. I just was, was saying--
坏了  我现在得走了  抱歉
Oh shit, I really gotta go, I'm sorry.
这些都很好
Look, this was all awesome,
我也很感激你  但我
and I really appreciate it, but I just--
但你不想和他们
But you, But you don't wanna talk to the--
不想和那些疯狂的人谈心是吗
you don't wanna talk to the crazy guy, right?
当然不是
No!
像我爸爸
Like, my dad
曾经也像你一样做这些事  但
used to take a lot of the stuff that you were, um...
是吗  那很棒
Oh! Cool!
我的意思是  不是说你爸爸
I mean, not cool that your dad was
像我一样去做这些就很棒  是说
like, I mean, like me, but it's just cool that--
我真的得走了
Okay, I really have to go.
我要赶上10点15的车到小镇的另一头去
I've gotta catch the 10:15 across town, so
抱歉  但谢谢你
sorry, but thank you!
你为什么要坐
Why, why're you cro--
坐那班车去那么远
the 10:15 across town,
为什么
why're you gonna do that?
因为这是最快的办法了
Because it's the fastest way across town.
为什么大家都自以为
Yo, why do guys always think that
他们知道最快的路呢
they know the fastest way around?
不  我是  一名司机
No! I'm-- I'm a driver!
我有四星的高评价
Yeah! I have a perfect four star rating.
我不需要你载我
I don't need a ride from you.
你已经帮我很多了
You've already done enough.
说真的  我能帮你  你一个人不行的
Seriously, I got you. You're not gonna make it.
你可能连公交车都赶不上
You'll probably miss the bus, and uh,
而且我是一名好司机  我可以带你去那里
I'm a good driver. I can take you.
所以呢  你是要我用"滴滴"下订单吗
So, what? Do I like, "app" you, or something?
不需要  我自己说了算  走吧
No! I'm my own boss. Let's go.
我开得很快
And I'm fast!
而且安全  又快又安全
Safe! Safe and fast.
我到了  谢谢你
Cool. Well, thank you.
你的车很舒适
This was-- you know your car is so nice.
-当然  -你也非常贴心
- Yeah. - And it was very sweet of you.
谢谢你夸我  这是我认识人的方式
Yeah, thank you. This is something I do to meet people.
他们都说和别人谈心对我有益
They say it's good for you to talk to people
因为我的心结
'cause this stuff, uh--
-对  -但你  会综合格斗
- Sure, Ok. - But you-- uh, the MMA.
是一种规则极为开放的竞技格斗运动
MMA：综合格斗，即mixed martial arts
你是直接和小伙子们打吗
Like, you straight roll with dudes?
对  有时候是
Yeah, sometimes. Yeah.
那也太牛了  酷毙了
That's badass. That's badass.
对  但是和女孩格斗更好
Yeah. I mean, sometimes it's actually better to fight with girls,
不像男孩子会不好意思下手
they put up more of a fight.
我很想  很想看一场格斗
I'd like to-- I'd like to see that.
你们会在训练馆格斗吗
I mean, do you-- at the gym do you guys have fights?
比如格斗比赛  什么的
Like matches? Fi-- fighting matches?
你喜欢格斗吗
You like fights?
我  我连一只苍蝇都打不过
I mean, me personally, I couldn't hurt a fly,
比起自己上场  我更喜欢观看别人格斗
but I like, I mean I think I'd like to like, watch it.
你懂的  因为观看格斗比赛
You know, 'cause it's-- the fighting,
就有一种  血脉偾张的感觉
to see the fighting is like, you know, it's like, cathartic!
我想想  我的训练馆在举办一场
Um, well, uh, my gym is hosting a tournament
为期大概两周的比赛
in about two weeks.
是女子综合格斗比赛
It's a female MMA tournament.
真的吗  全女性吗
What? Like an all-girl blood sport?
就像完全的对打风格吗
Like, straight Kumite style?
我不清楚  那是什么意思
I don't know, I don't know what that means.
那  你会参加吗
Well, are-- are you gonna be in it?
你认真的吗
Am I gonna be in it?
我当然不会参加  那可是一场大比赛
Uh, no! That's like, that's like a big-- no.
你肯定得参加啊
You, you should totally be in it.
不不不  我还只是个训练生
I'm not like-- that's not. I just-- I just train.
什么  为什么不去参加  你得上啊
What? I mean, why not? You tol-- you totally should do it.
我  算了吧
I'm-- no. I'm not--
我没那么优秀  还没到那个水平
I'm not that good. I'm not at that level, so, um...
但听着  我真的
But hey look, man, I really--
我得走了
I have to get going.
如果你真的想看比赛
If you do wanna go see it,
下周会在会议中心举办
it's next week at the convention center.
我会去的  我去定了
I'm there! I'm there. So there.
这是发生在我人生中
This is like the-- this is like the greatest thing
最棒的一件事了
to happen to mankind, ever!
那好  就这样吧  再见  谢谢你载我
Okay, cool. Bye, thank you.
再见  我们应该  一起去
Bye! We-- we should go.
我告诉过你这蠢女人会上钩的
I told you this bitch be hookin'.
太神了
Shit.
我们都想赚钱  但是
Like, we all tryna get money, but damn.
绝对不是那样赚的
I mean, not-- not like that.
我把你安排在一点
I got you set up at one.
那时你应该打扫到207号房了对吧
You'll be in room 207 by then?
对  应该是的  房主是谁
Uh, yeah. Should be. Who is it?
管那么多干什么  你先管好你自己
The fuck you care? Just do your thing.
姑娘  这沙包惹到你了吗
Damn, girl! What'd that bag do to you?
拜托  冠军可不是一蹴而就的
Shit! Champs aren't built overnight,
你明白吧
you know what I'm sayin'?
-我明白  -你汗都没流呢
- You right. - You're not even sweating!
我知道  因为我一直全力以赴锻炼
I know. 'Cause I've been putting in that work.
一天六个小时  会比你们轻松一些
Six hours a day, that's what it does.
真好  我也想像你一样
Yeah, man. I just wanna get like you.
-那你最好开始训练  -好的
- Then you better start training! - You're right.
-知道了  -快点
- You're right. - Hustle up!
好了  过会见
Alright, see ya!
你看什么呢  动起来
What you lookin' at? C'mon!
让我看看你技术怎么样
Let's see your stand up game!
双手就位
Hands up.
你得把臀部也用上
Alright, you gotta put your hips
集中力量
into that shit, step into it.
好
Okay.
下巴收起来一些
Alright, chin down. A little lower.
保持肘部紧绷
Keep the elbows tight.
要紧凑在一起  好好做
No, don't spread like that! What the fuck?
呼吸  让我听到你的呼吸声
Breathe. Breathe! Let me hear you.
不是要你蛮力出拳
Okay, it's not about hitting it so damn hard.
注意技巧
It's all technique.
带动臀部
Turn your hips.
很好  再来
Okay, a little more.
伸展出去
Longer extension.
胳膊肘要带到位置
Put your elbows in,
带到位置  很好
bring your elbows in. Okay.
你打得越来越好了
You're puttin' in some work!
诺拉  阿依莎  可以了
Nora, Aisha, you're up!
我们来练柔术  来吧  姑娘们
Let's work on some jiu-jitsu. Let's go, girls!
谢谢
Thanks.
牛奶钱呢
What about the milk?
不好意思
Right.
诺拉  我不需要保姆
I don't need a babysitter, Nora.
谢谢
Thank you.
不  妈妈  我工作的时候
Yes, you do, mom. You know I don't like to
我不想只留你一人
leave you alone while I'm at work.
她玩牌耍赖
She cheats at cards.
就像一个恶臭的婊子
She cheats like a dirty fucking whore.
妈妈
Mom.
-怎么了  -别说了
- Yes. - Stop.
她啥也不干一天就能赚20块钱
Twenty dollars a day for what?
就是每天坐着  出老千
To sit on her ass, cheating at cards
下午还一直睡觉
and taking long naps in the afternoon!
妈妈
Mom!
你应该庆幸雇她不用30块
Look, just be glad it's not thirty dollars, okay?
先吃饭吧  我马上回来
Eat your food, I'll be right back.
又是鸡肉
Chicken again.
该死  给我点钱
Dammit, give me the money
也许我们能吃上一顿好的
and maybe we can eat a decent meal!
我操
The fuck?
-她又来了  -你他妈在逗我吧
- She's in there again! - Are you fucking kidding me?
在休息呢  不开玩笑  真来了
On a break! No, I'm dead serious!
天呐  快把她赶走
God damn, let's get this bitch out of here.
真晦气
Shit!
你觉得这可能吗
It's like, is it possible?
她必须滚蛋  就现在
She needs to go, she needs to go.
我受够了  快让她滚
You know, I'm tired of it, she needs to go.
你真的得滚蛋了
You need to go. Just like, honestly--
你什么毛病  一天都在休息
What the fuck man? All day!
请问您是偷懒女王吗
Breaks all day! Like, break queen.
能请您去工作吗
Can you do some work?
-要是你不想做  你可以  -我正准备去
- If you don't like it, you need - I was going to.
-是吗  -可你一直在休息
- Really? - You're always on break!
如果你不想待在这里
If you don't wanna be here,
-你可以滚  -滚蛋
- just don't be here! - Get out.
-停  -没人拦你
- Hey! - Then just don't be here!
你们吵什么呢
Hey, what's going on in here?
她什么工作也不做
She's not doing any fucking work!
就在这里偷懒
She's not working.
-她就会偷懒  -我们
- She's here, lounging and shit.- Are we the only
是这里唯一的女仆吗
maids you have here?
好了  听着  我要占用
Alright, look. I need the room
这个房间15分钟  你们俩  请出去
for fifteen minutes. You two, out.
诺拉  你留下
Nora, stick around.
-所以我们连休息都不配吗  -不休息吗
- So we don't get a break? - No break?
-15分钟就好  -是这样吗
- Come back in fifteen minutes. - In fifteen?
随你说
That means in fifteen,
我能再给你15分钟
I can have fifteen plus fifteen,
然后我们就可以像她一样休息30分钟吗
and have a thirty minute break like Nora?
你就是在放屁
This is bullshit!
-把门带上  -好  你说了算
- Close the door! - Yeah. I'll close it.
你还好吗
You okay?
我知道你最近
I know you've been going
有些难关要克服
through a lot of stuff here lately.
但我也得说说你的工作状态
I also have to say your work
直线下降了
has been slipping a lot.
很抱歉  我就是  有点累了
I'm sorry. I've just been a little tired.
是因为塔尼娅和萨沙的排挤吗
Tanya and Sasha giving you a hard time?
有点  但别担心
Yeah, but don't worry.
我能应付一切
It's nothing I can't handle.
你离她们远点
You stay away from those two.
她们是麻烦精
They are trouble.
我天天都是这么做的
I try to. Every day.
好  开始吧  注意走位
Alright, let's go. Move your feet!
诺拉  你表现很不错
Hey, Nora lookin' pretty good.
做得好  姑娘们
Man! Great job, ladies!
这就是我想看到的
That's what I'm talking about!
好了  你们做得很好
Alright, good job, girls.
诺拉  一点了
Yo! Nora! One o'clock.
我操
Fuck!
如果我再不接  他就要打爆我的电话了
What? He's gonna freak out if I don't pick up.
宝贝  我在训练呢
Hey, babe, I'm training.
等会给你回电吧
Can I call you back?
好  等会说
Okay, okay. Talk to you later.
我会回电的  拜拜
Yes, I'll call you back. Bye.
今天有个人来这里找你
There was a guy here looking for you today.
指定了找你
Specifically you.
他开着一辆好车  露齿大笑
Uh, nice car. Big smile, teeth.
你要是再见到他
Well, if you see him again,
直接报警  好吗
you call the cops. Alright?
应该不是什么麻烦精吧
Trouble? No?
不  只是另一件我要抗争的事
No. Just one more thing I have to fight.
小心点  诺拉
Be careful, Nora.
快  双脚动起来  诺拉
C'mon! Move your feet, Nora!
双手举起来  阿依莎
Get your hands up, Aisha.
这就对了  姑娘们  动起来
That's it, that's it! C'mon, girls, work!
我们距离
We got five days till
双打比赛只有五天了  加油
Double A Double A Tournament, let's go!
给我加油
C'mon!
别胡闹了  使出力气
Quit pissin' around! Let's go!
你能赢  姐妹
You got this, girl.
那比赛她已经稳了
She's ready for this thing, man.
-她要出招了  -妙极了
- She's got something goin' for her. - Nice.
-上啊  -兄弟  我被惊到了
- Okay! - I'm surprised, dude.
快  菜鸟  继续打呀
Okay. Okay, rookie! Go ahead!
集中注意  重拳出击
Pay attention! Get your hands up!
对了  就是这样
That's it, that's it!
注意  小心
Watch it! Oh.
结束了  别打了
Okay, that's it, that's it.
还得从头再来
Yup. Back to the drawing board.
诺拉  你还好吗
Nora, you good?
我没事  实战的时候我分神了
Nah, it's all good. We were sparring, and I just got distracted.
我去  还在流血吗
Damn! It's still bleeding?
是啊  好像止不住了
Yeah, I think so. Yeah, it's not stopping.
我看看
Here.
阿依莎  不用  你不用帮我
Oh, no. Aisha, you don't have to do that.
不行
I know. But I am.
抬头  抬头
Lean back. Lean back.
疼吗
Does that hurt?
疼
Ow!
你这个小婊子
You're such a little bitch.
闭嘴  也许我只对你婊
Shut up! To you, maybe.
我得再检查一下
Okay. I'm gonna try one more thing.
想确定看看骨头断没断
I just want to make sure it's not broken.
-这样疼吗  -不疼
- Does that hurt? - No.
这是第一次被撂倒吗
Is this your first time?
不是
No.
你以前也被打倒过
You've been knocked out before?
不是
Oh, no.
以前被打过吗
Gotten beat up before?
不  有过
Uh, no-- yeah.
过两天还是个漂亮鼻子
Gonna be a nice one.
对不起  我以为你也对我有意思
I'm sorry. I thought that's what you wanted.
真的  我真的很抱歉
Hey, look. I'm really sorry.
我不是想越界
I didn't mean to cross the line.
你要知道我很尊重你  打心眼里尊重你
Look, I want you to know I respect you, wholeheartedly,
我很感激你们为我所做的一切
and I'm so appreciative for everything you guys have done for me.
我们
You guys?
是啊  你  罗辛  还有这个训练馆
Yeah! You, and Rosheen and the gym.
所以你是随便跟人上床吗
So you just go and make out with everybody?
当然不是
No!
我关心你  是因为你是我的训练搭档
I'm lookin' out for you 'cause you're my sparring partner.
目前是而已
For now.
我在和你搭档训练  就这么简单
'Cause I'm training with you. That's it.
是我会错意了  就这样
I just misread things, that's all.
所以你乱亲已经结婚的人吗
So you just kiss people who are married?
那你快乐吗
Well, are you happy?
你的婚姻幸福吗
With your marriage?
从我面前滚开  诺拉
Get outta my face, Nora.
滚开  诺拉
对不起  阿依莎
I'm sorry, Aisha.
蛋黄酱是由十个字母组成的吗
What is a ten letter word for mayonnaise?
我觉得这个应该是填蛋黄酱
'Cause I think it's fucking mayonnaise.
不然还会是哪个单词
What other-- what other word could that be?
-这应该是个陷阱  -我要去跑步了
- I think it's a trick. - Hey, I'm going for my run.
你在家可以吗
You gonna be okay?
当然可以  我自己来  你去跑步吧
Yeah, yeah. No, no, no. You go for your run.
要不是我快死了  我也想和你一起去
I would go with you, except for this whole, shitty dying thing.
一点都不好笑  妈妈
You know, it's not funny, mom.
我不知道你是不是在说反话
I can't tell if you're being sarcastic or not.
我懂的  没人愿意坐在这儿看我自暴自弃
I get it. Who wants to sit around watching me fall apart anymore?
你去跑步吧  没事的
So you run, it's fine.
你知道我最近在训练呢
Look, you know that I'm training right now.
训练啥  摔跤吗
For what? Wrestling?
这不只是摔跤  我在这方面真的很有天赋
It's not just wrestling. I'm actually getting pretty good at this.
好吧  这对你将来有什么好处
Okay. So where's that lead?
或许成为职业选手呢  我也不知道
A career? I don't know.
有人真的可以以此为生  衣食无忧
Some people actually make really good money at this.
也是  但只有佼佼者才能做到  对吧
Okay, but really good people, right?
我就是佼佼者
I am good.
诺拉  你脸上的神情
Your face, Nora.
是佼佼者应该有的吗
Is that a sign that you're good?
实际上训练馆有不少人觉得
Well, actually, there are a few people at the gym who think
我应该去参加即将举行的MMA锦标赛
that I should join the upcoming MMA tournament, so yeah.
所以  我很强
So I am.
MMA  指的是混合蟒蛇武打
MMA. Is that mixed martial anaconda?
此处三个名词英文缩写皆同为MMA
棉花糖硬汉阿伯克龙比
Masculine marshmallow Abercrombie?
还是  欠操的王八蛋
Motherfuckin' manly assholes?
听着  我要去跑步了  你自己在家行吗
Look, I'm gonna go for my jog. Are you gonna be alright?
当然  你一个人行吗
Yeah, I will be. Will you?
你确认申请吗
是
否
诺拉  一点行吗
Yo, yo, yo, Nora! One o'clock?
今天不行
Not today, man.
我告诉过你  打拳挣不了什么钱
Man, I told you that boxing shit is no good for business.
也许有人就喜欢被揍的感觉
I mean, maybe some dude's into that black eye stuff,
自己照照镜子看看
but come on man, look at you.
全是伤  人都肿了  跟个男人一样
You're all jacked up and swolled up like a dude.
随便吧  我要休息  我上周末打了一场
Well, I gotta lay off anyways. I got a fight this weekend.
不行  一堆破事已经够让我烦的了
No, no, no, no, no. This shit messes me up, man!
-听着  -我该给这家伙说什么
- Look - What am I supposed to tell this guy?
我不知道  就说我突然得了性病  随便编
I don't know! Tell him I have a blistering STD or some shit.
操
Fuck, man!
好吧
Aight.
歇一周  行吧
Alright, one week, okay?
一周之后照常上班
One week, and then we back to business as usual.
听着  黑修斯
Look, Jesus.
我一直在想  你别误会
I been thinking and, and-- don't take this the wrong way.
这真的
It's just, um,
我不确定我是不是还想干这个
I'm not real sure I wanna keep doing this.
你他妈说的什么屁话
The fuck you talking about?
我们说好的  这还是你定的
We got a deal here. A good deal! You making
你现在想反悔吗
change, ain't you?
是啊  可你也没按我们说好的来啊
Yeah. But how much change are you making on this?
这是我应得的  我安排好  让一切照常
I get my share! I set this shit up, I keep it goin'--
是我在你干那档子事时帮你盯梢的
I'm the one who watches your ass when you conductin' business,
所以怎样  我拿走了我应得的
so fuck yeah, I'm gonna get my share!
我也要吃饭啊  不然我咋办
I gotta eat too, right? What am I supposed to do?
算了  我再多给你加十块  行吧
Alright, I'm gonna get you ten more a pop, okay?
再加十块  不说了
Ten more a pop, and that's it.
再加钱  有的哥们用这个价可以去市中心
Any more than that, these dudes can go downtown
找个俱乐部小姐玩了
and get club pussy for that price.
行了  黑修斯
Alright, Jesus.
随便你怎么想  好吧
Think whatever you want, alright,
但真没什么人想要操你
but nobody wants your ass that bad.
你知道吗  黑修斯
Then you know what, Jesus?
以后也没人可以操到我  你说呢
Ain't nobody gonna get me then, how 'bout that?
我操
Fuck!
我知道你都干了什么
I know what you be doin'.
你知道个屁
You don't know shit.
我当然知道
Oh, I know.
你以为没人知道
You think that nobody's gonna find out
你在这偷偷摸摸干什么吗
what the fuck you doin' around here?
黑修斯想让我也干这个
Shit, Jesus tried to get me to do that same shit.
我操  我跟他说没可能
And I was like, "Nah, fuck that!" No, bitch.
贱人别这么看我  我可没你这么贱干这个
Don't look at me like that, like I couldn't. Like you.
你就不能让我一个人待一会吗
Why can't you just leave me alone?
不能  我他妈烦死你了  你整天牛逼哄哄
Because I don't fuckin' like you. You're entitled.
自私自利  感觉好像这地方是你家一样
You're mean. You walk around here like you own this shit.
这旅馆才不是你的地盘
You don't own no-- the fuckin' hotel!
你很讨人厌  你很贱
You're not nice. You're a bitch!
-我贱吗  -你贱
- I'm a bitch? - You a bitch.
你是不知道自己几斤几两吗
Is there like, a fake mirror here
你才下贱  照照镜子吧你
or something? 'Cause you're the bitch!
要我照镜子  婊子  我知道我贱
A fake mirror? Bitch, I know I'm a bitch!
我就想告诉你  你也好不到哪儿去
I just letting you know that you are a bitch.
-知道不  还坐在台阶上  -好吧  我他妈
- Okay? Sitting on the steps. - Well, I don't give
才不管你讨厌什么
a shit what you don't like.
发飙了吗
Oh! You gettin' tough now?
你要发飙了吗  要揍我吗
You tough? You 'bout to do somethin'?
你绝逼摊上事儿了
I'm guessin' that you got somethin' coming to you.
打一架吗
Let's go.
你以为我要在上班时候跟你打架吗
You think I'm finna fight you right now at my job?
干吗不打
Why not?
现实生活告诉我们真正的成年人
Um, real adults in real life actually
只关心的是挣多少钱
care about getting paid for shit.
没人会搞砸自己的工作搞得自己挣不了钱
All of us can't fuck for work and for money.
我还得上班呢
So I need this job.
你现在没事  你很快就会摊上事的
So, it's not gon' be today, not here, but it's comin' to you.
你他妈活该
'Cause you fuckin' deserve it.
别四处晃荡讨人嫌
Walkin' around here like your shift don't stink.
你屁都不是  你个贱人
You ain't nothin', bitch.
你和我们没什么区别  干的都是下贱活儿
You just like the rest of us bitches,
挨个房间去打扫
walkin' around here, cleaning rooms.
记着这一点  知道不  神经病
Get that through your skull, how 'bout that? Fuckin' psycho.
懒得像屎一样  诺拉
Lazy as shit Nora.
继续吧  喝你的苏打
Go ahead, drink your soda.
喝着呢
I plan on it.
没你的活儿是吧
Got nothin' to be done around here, right?
这是我的休息时间  谁管你
I'm on my break, I don't know about you.
可不是呢
Yeah.
谁都想像你这样休息
Wish we all had a break like you.
伙计们  投入一点  手举高
Alright, guys, get in here. Keep those hands up.
教练  再给他们加二十组
Give 'em another twenty, coach.
我收到了弃权申请  所以你去参加比赛吗
I got a waiver request for you to enter the tournament.
是吗  你要参加吗
Is that right? You entered?
是
Yeah.
行吧
Alright.
随便你
Why not?
我妈呢
Where's my mother?
回来了
Oh, hey.
是啊
Hello.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
彼得斯太太
Oh! Mrs. Peters?
怎么了
Yes?
我这几天可能没法给你日结了
Um, I'm not gonna have the money to pay for the next few days.
下周一次性结清行吗
Would it be okay if I just paid you in full next week?
这可和当初约定的不一样
That's not our arrangement.
我知道  我希望你能理解一下
I know, um, I was kinda hopin' you'd help me out
仅此一次而已
and it'd be like a one-time thing.
当初我们之所以约定好就是为了双方
The reason arrangements are made is so that
都能清楚自己的权利和义务
all the parties involved know what's expected of them.
-我知道  我只是想  -我的个老天  玛丽
- I know, I just thought that may - Jesus Christ, Mary!
她说了下周给你付钱
If she says she's gonna pay you next week,
那她肯定给你
she'll pay you next week!
别这么操蛋行吗
Don't be such a fucking dickweed!
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
-彼得斯太太  -什么事
- Oh, and Mrs. Peters? - Yes?
我周六晚上有点事
I also have something this Saturday night.
又来  我不同意
Again, not agreed to!
我知道  就这一次
I know, but it's just a one-time thing.
两倍工钱
Double.
你他妈的在碰瓷吧  玛丽
Oh, jump in front of a fucking truck, Mary.
没问题  两倍就两倍
That's fine! Double, that's totally fine.
谢谢你  彼得斯太太
Thank you, Mrs. Peters. Thank you.
这个婊子太贱了
Oh, she is such a bitch!
够了  别再说了
Too much. Stop it with all that.
我不  她扰乱了我积极向上的正能量
No! She is messing with my positive healing energy.
要知道如果你和绝症病人打牌
You know, if you're going to play cards with the terminally ill,
你至少输几把  这是礼貌
you should at least lose a few hands. It's only polite.
妈  你玩牌很烂
Just 'cause you suck at cards, mom,
不代表人家出千了
doesn't mean that she's a cheater.
她牌技也不咋地
She has no fucking class.
我过去也很强壮
Aw, I used to be strong.
我也有胸
I used to have boobs.
现在屁都没了
This shit just eats everything.
诺拉  告诉我
Nora, tell me...
你胜算有多大
What are your odds in this thing?
要知道  我的意思是  如果你比我
'Cause, you know, it'll be weird
先死的话  就太不合理了
if you die before I do. That's all I'm sayin'.
妈妈  我是在为你而战
Mom, I'm fighting for you.
赢了会有一大笔钱的
You know, this is a lot of money.
宝贝  不要为我
Honey, don't fight for me.
为你自己而战
Fight for you.
这病已经发展到第四阶段了
This is stage four.
他妈的第四阶段啊
Stage four of fucking four.
等你战胜疾病的时候  你会感谢我的
Yeah, well, you'll thank me when you overcome the odds.
我谁都不谢
Oh, I won't be here to thank anyone.
那你到时候准备做什么
And then what are you gonna do? Hm?
妈妈
Mom--
听着  诺拉  我快死了
Look, Nora, I'm gonna die
也许活不过两个月了
and it'll probably be in the next two months.
你得制定个现实点的计划
And you need a realistic plan.
我不听你在这胡说八道
I'm not listening to this shit.
我死了之后你会失去这座房子
You will lose this house without my disability
到那时你要去哪呢
then where are you gonna go?
做什么呢
What are you gonna do?
我有计划
I have a plan.
我要赢下这场比赛  把钱拿到手
I'm gonna win this tournament, I'm gonna win the money,
然后带你去接受合适的治疗
and I'm gonna get you the proper care that you need!
亲爱的  这计划不现实
Oh, honey, that's not real.
只能算是个梦罢了
That's just a dream.
那也是我的梦  别想把它从我身边夺走
Well, it's my dream. Stop trying to take it away from me.
嘿  诺拉
Hey! Nora!
是我  是杰森
Yo! Hey, it's me! It-- It's Jason!
你好啊  杰森  那个  我得去上班了
Oh, hey, what's up, Jason? Yeah, I gotta go to work.
那个  等一下  就一会
No, hey, wait! Wait one second, though!
兄弟  有什么事吗
What do you want, man?
我
Um, i--
听着  我很感激
Look, I already thanked you
你替我付钱买了我妈妈要用的药
for helping with my mom's medication.
但我实在是没有什么可以报答你的
I really have nothing else I can give you.
只是
I just--
只是你在我脑海里挥之不去
I just can't stop thinking about you.
但  我是说  不是
But-- I mean, not--
不是像有些傻逼一样
I mean, not in like in some crazy person way.
像一些  一些不速之客
Some like, some guy who just
突然出现在你工作的地方
just shows up at your work unannounced.
我  我跟他们不一样
No, not like that guy
我更像是一个
but more like the guy who
精神正常的人  是发自内心地觉得
is well-balanced on his meds and he just really thinks
你是一个非常酷的女孩子
that you're this super cool chick and would love to get a chance
想进一步了解你而已
to get to know you better kind of way.
听着  我很抱歉  你看上去人不错
Look, I'm sorry. You seem nice.
但我不欠你什么
That doesn't mean I owe you anything.
我应该穿V领衬衫来的
I shoulda wore the V-neck!
真该穿那件V领衬衫来
I should've worn the V-neck.
操
I--
没关系  还可以  表现得还可以
You know, it could've-- coulda gone worse. Coulda gone worse.
好  再给我一周  可以吗  我
Aight, give me another week, alright? I--
好的好的  兄弟冷静一下好吗
Alright. Alright, man, don't be a tough guy, alright?
你  如果你  好吧
Do you-- If you-- Alright.
好吧  没错  会给你安排的
Okay, you're right, you got it.
没错  下午三点之后的任何时间均可入住
Yes, sir! Anytime, after 3 PM, check-in!
非常好  直接过来  我们会为您安排食宿
Very good, uh, just stop by and we can accommodate.
好的  谢谢您
Very good. Thanks.
伯恩斯先生
Uh, Mr. Burns?
诺拉  有什么事吗
Ah, Nora! Um, what can I do for you?
跟萨沙又起冲突了吗  请坐
Oh. More problems with Sasha? Have a seat.
不  那个  我想在周六请天假
No. Um, I actually need to ask for Saturday off.
星  星期
Satur--
这周星期六
This Saturday?
没错
Yeah
你也知道星期六是咱们这最忙的一天
Saturday, you know, is our busiest day of the week.
那事对你很重要吗
Is it-- Is it that important to you?
-对  挺重要的  -你让我很难办啊
- Yeah, it really is. - Aw, you're killin' me here.
诺拉  真难办啊  你
You're killin' me, Nora! You--
这周六会特别忙
Saturday we're gonna be especially busy.
让我考虑一下  好吗  我会
Um. I will think about it, okay? I will--
我不知道现在能不能给你答复
I don't know if I can deal with this now.
我想一想  我会  会给你答复的
I'll think about it. I'll, I'll let you know.
伯恩斯先生  我从未请过假
Mr. Burns, I never ask for time off.
我知道  我知道
I know that, I know that.
但你是我这最好的员工  我还能怎么办
But you're my best girl. I-- What am I gonna do?
我一直在给你干活  我只想要一天的假期
I'm here for you all the time! All I'm asking is for one day.
星期六
Saturday.
对
Yes.
看来这周六一定会很忙
It's gonna be really busy Saturday.
谢谢你  伯恩斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Burns.
你欠我一次
Hey-- you owe me!
好吧  显然我现在谁都欠
Eh, apparently I owe everyone.
那个穿衬衫的是谁
Who was the suit?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
灰宝马车里那个时尚先生
Mr. GQ in the grey beamer!
啥  你在跟我耍心眼吗  诺拉
What, you back-doorin' me, Nora?
没有
No!
那他妈那个衬衫男是谁
Then who's the fuckin' suit?
他就是一个我前几天遇到的路人
He's just some guy I met!
一个路人  我的天啊
Some guy, my ass!
什么  你觉得你能把中间人排除在外
What? You think you can cut out the middle man?
自立门户  是吗
Huh? Start your own lil' business?
不行  你想卖  你也得通过我去卖
Nah, you wanna deal, you deal through me.
我没有卖  他只是个我见过的路人
I'm not dealing! He's just some guy I met!
你刚刚遇见一个富佬  是吗
You just met some rich ass guy, right?
撒谎至少也装得像一点啊
If you're gonna lie, at least make it convincing.
你这话什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你以为凯子那么好钓吗
No suit goes bottom trollin'!
再他妈背着我搞小动作
I catch you fuckin' around my back again
我就搞死你  诺拉
I'm gonna mess you up, Nora.
你管不到我  懂吗  你离我远点行吗
Yo, you don't own me, alright? Why don't you back up?
你他妈干什么
The fuck you doin'?
你他妈疯了是吗  想造反是吗
You fuckin' crazy, huh? Fucking crazy?
-他们在打架吗  -天啊  还真的
- Are they fighting? - Oh yeah, they are.
-我操  我操  这他妈的  -什么鬼
- Oh, shit! Oh, shit! Oh shit! - What the fuck?
我操  还手啊  黑修斯  你跟个傻逼一样
Oh my god! Hit back, Jesus! You look stupid!
-你被打的真惨  -别打了
- You're gettin' your ass beat! - Enough!
你个怂逼  黑修斯  真是疯了
You a pussy, Jesus, that's crazy.
她都骑你脸上了
She just molly wopped you.
他啥也没干  就在那挨打
He didn't do nothin', he just stood there!
是啊  你被揍惨了
Yeah, you got fucked up.
去你们妈的
Fuck y'all!
被揍惨了吧
Got your ass kicked!
我没被揍惨
I didn't get my ass kicked!
滚你妈的  我操
Fuck you-- oh shit!
-我操  -我的天
- Oh shit! - Oh! Oh shit!
不  不  你要死了  他完蛋了
Nope! Nope, you're dead. He's fucked up.
你要死了  没法呼吸了都  兄弟
You're gonna die, you can't breathe. Damn!
你最好反抗一下  黑修斯  起来啊
Better stand up, Jesus! Stand up!
这他妈怎么  这怎么回事
What the hell is go-- What is going on here?
让她离我远点
Get her off me!
黑修斯  停手  你给我从她身上下来
Jesus, stop it, and you get off of her right now!
我  我吗  她在锁
I'm ch-- me? She's cho--!
给我  给我分开  你俩
Get-- Break it up, you two!
快点  都正常点  我的天啊
C'mon! Behave like humans, for crying out loud!
黑修斯  来我办公室  马上
Jesus! In my office, right now!
去她妈的
Man, fuck her!
现在  快给我滚去办公室
I said now! Get the hell in my office!
还有你俩
And you two!
萨沙  这不关你的事  给我
Sasha, mind your own business! Get--
不  不  这就是我的事  伯恩斯先生
No. No! This is my business, Mr. Burns!
你知道吗  你总是对她偏心
You know, you-- you're always playing favorites!
但你知道吗  你的小宝贝就在这几间房里
And you know, your favorite has been fuckin' Johns in these rooms
夜以继日地在你眼皮底下操着男人
night after night for months right under your nose!
没错
That's right.
-现在感觉如何  -别客气  我们告诉你了
- How you feel about that? - You're welcome, we told you.
诺拉  是真的吗
Nora, is this true?
诺拉  我问你话呢
Nora, I'm talking to you.
告诉我这不是真的
Just tell me it is not true.
天呐
Oh, God.
完了  完了哦
Yep. Boom.
你俩  回去工作  给我滚
You two, get back to work. Get-- go!
你这人  你只是
You just-- you just-
现在知道了吧
Got the truth now.
别客气哦
You're welcome.
该休息的我都让你休息了
I give you every break in the book
然后你就这么对我吗
and this is what you do to me?
别管那些嫖客了  你真伤我心
Forget the Johns, you fucked me!
我本来以为你还不至于堕落至此
I thought you were better than that.
收拾好东西走吧  你被开除了
Just get your shit and go. You do not work here anymore.
把手抬起来  诺拉  加油  加油啊
Get your hands up, Nora! C'mon! C'mon!
-打我啊  -保持步伐  保持移动
- Come here! - Keep moving, keep moving!
怎么回事
What the hell?
你光站那挨打怎么参加比赛
Why'd you enter the tournament if you're just gonna stand there?
你他妈怎么回事  诺拉
The fuck is your problem, Nora?
我没事
I don't have a problem!
你说你没事  你他妈什么意思
What do you mean you don't have a fuckin' problem?
我看你他妈有一堆破事
You got a big ass problem!
打起精神
Come on!
你连罗辛都打不过  还打什么比赛啊
You entered the competition and you can't even beat Rosheen!
天啊  你说啥
Oh, co-- What?
你不想打就别他妈参赛了
You don't have to fight in this fuckin' competition!
我他妈别无选择了懂吗  别无选择了
I don't fuckin' have a choice. I don't fucking have a choice!
诺拉你到底要不要打  还是你想
Are you girls gonna fight or Nora, you need me to string you up
让我把你吊起来给别人当沙袋打  振作点
and let everyone use you as a punching bag? Come on!
-我在打了  -你他妈在打个鬼
- I am fighting! - No, you're fuckin' not!
你跟我打啊  诺拉  出手啊  打啊  打啊
Then fight, Nora! Fuckin' fight! Fight! Fight, Nora!
注意点
Come on.
好了  别打了
Alright, that's enough!
你他妈打啊
Fuckin' fight!
够了够了  别打了  起来起来起来
That's enough! Let it go! Get up! Get up! Get up!
-你他妈打啊  -够了
- Fuckin' fight! - Come on.
-够了够了  冷静点  -你他妈打啊
- Come on, let it go! - Fuckin' fight!
-她什么也不干  -给我去走一圈
- She ain't doin' shit! - Take a fuckin' walk!
她他妈什么也不做
She's not fuckin' doin' shit!
就他妈快比赛了
This is the tournament!
-给我出去冷静冷静  -对啊都快比赛了
- Get your ass out and take a walk! - Yes!it is!
起来
Get up.
不不不  你进来  你他妈怎么回事
No, no, no. Get in here. The fuck's goin' on with you?
没事  我挺好的
Nothing. I'm fine.
振作起来
Get it together.
好吗
Aight?
对不起  阿依莎
I'm sorry, Aisha.
我不是故意搞砸你训练的
I didn't mean to mess up your training.
我只是最近什么都搞砸了
It's just I'm messing everything up nowadays.
别再自怨自艾了
Stop feeling sorry for yourself
想要什么就他妈去奋斗
and fight for what the fuck you really want.
可是我现在不知道我到底想要什么了
Yeah, I don't know what I want anymore.
妈
Mom?
彼得斯太太  你是在睡觉吗
Mrs. Peters, were you sleeping?
你听见我妈在咳嗽了吗
Is that my mom coughing?
你本来应该去照看她的
You're supposed to be watching her!
天啊
Jesus!
妈妈  妈妈
Mom. Hey! Mom!
妈妈  醒醒  你还好吗
Mom, wake up. Mom. You okay?
没事  没事  我挺好的
No, no, I'm okay.
很正常  不就是每天都觉得我快死了
This is normal, everyday death spiral shit.
你真没事吗
You're okay?
是的  没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
好吧  我给你带晚饭了
Alright, 'cause I brought you dinner.
让我猜猜  还是鸡肉
Oh! Let me guess, chicken!
不对  我给你带了
No, I brought you hamburgers
你最喜欢吃的汉堡
because I know they're your favorite.
确实是我最喜欢的  谢谢你
Aw, that they are. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
说吧
Spit it out.
我今天被开除了
I got fired today.
为什么
For what?
因为打架
For fighting.
工作的时候打架
Fighting at work.
不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
我只是在维护自己
You know, I just was standing up for myself
只是稍微起了点肢体冲突
and it got a little physical,
就这样
that's all.
那你打的一定是个烦人的自恋狂吧
Well, that must have been a dandy of a brouhaha.
听着  妈妈
Look, Mom.
没了这工作我不知道要怎么满足日常开销
I don't know how I'm gonna pay for everything without this job.
我都不知道怎么给玛丽工资
I don't even know how I'm gonna pay Mary back!
哎哟  去她妈的吧
Oh, fuck that cow.
她能拿你怎么办  起诉你吗
What is she gonna do to you, sue ya?
为了什么  就这破地
For what? This shithole?
听着  你还会找到其他工作的  诺拉
No. You will find something else, Nora.
我只想让咱俩过得更好
I just want better for us.
那好吧
Well then,
我想你现在只剩一个选项了
I guess there's only one thing you can do.
拿下比赛
Win that damn tournament.
把那该死的综合什么什么玩意赢下来
Win that whole goddamn MM-- Mountain Man Asshole thing.
去把她们打得落花流水
You go kick everybody's goddamn ass.
诺拉  这是你的遣散费
Hey, Nora. I have your, uh, severance check here.
好
Cool.
你一定恨透我了  对吧
You're pissed at me, huh?
本来我可以去报案的
I coulda called the law on you,
那你就得去蹲局子了  知道吗
you'd been in jail. You know that?
现在看来  黑修斯很可能会去起诉你
As it is, Jesus is probably gonna press charges.
黑修斯才不会去报警
Jesus is not gonna call the cops.
也许会  也许不会
Yeah, maybe.
但你和同事打架一定是错的
But you just can't beat the hell out of a coworker.
解决不了问题
It's never the answer.
你想象不到我已经被逼得走投无路了
Well, you don't know how far I was pushed.
我想我知道
I can guess.
我能猜出来
因为你觉得自己是对的  就有理由打人吗
Hurting somebody just 'cause you think you're right?
简直就是坐上了牢房直通车  孩子
That is a fast track to a criminal record, kid.
真好  生活中不止奋斗[打架]
Yeah, well, that'd just be one more
现在还得多听你几句屁话
bullshit thing that I have to fight.
为什么
Why?
所有的事情到你这  就要打架解决  诺拉
Why does it always have to be a fight with you, Nora?
因为一切都要靠奋斗[打架]  比利
Because everything is a fight, Billy!
对  对  你一直就这么说的
Yes, yes, you keep telling me.
简直不懂你对这两个字的定义
I question your definition of "fight"!
转动臀部  拜托
Rotate that hip. C'mon.
好  表现不错  姑娘们  今天就到这儿吧
Alright, good job girls. That's the day.
-谢谢教练  -不客气
- Thank you, Coach! - Yep.
阿依莎  诺拉  轮到你俩上了
Aisha, Nora! You're up!
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  姑娘们  游戏时间到了
Alright ladies, it's game time.
明天下午两点
Two o'clock tomorrow evenin',
我在文娱中心等你们俩
I'll meet you both at the Civic Center and
到时候一切见分晓
we'll see what we see.
但就目前来说
But for right now, however,
你们给我打起万分精神
I need you to really concentrate on
投入到自己的动作和步法中去
your structure and your footwork.
今晚  就好好休息
Tonight, get your rest.
至少都要睡够八小时
Eight hours at least, please.
如果想的话  也可以多睡会
Maybe more, if you can.
然后  早上可以去跑一跑
And then, maybe a light run in the morning,
小憩一下  然后就该你们展现自我了
a nap, and then it's show time.
还有什么问题吗
You girls got any questions?
-没有  教练  -好的  放松点
- No, Coach. - Alright. Take it easy.
-嘿  阿依莎  -怎么
- Hey, Aisha? - Sup?
我想说  昨天的事我真的很抱歉
Just wanted to say I'm really sorry about yesterday.
不  你没错  是我有点太过分了
Nah, you're good. I was a little too hard on you.
不  我说真的
Nah, it was good.
因为你  我总算意识到我想要什么
You really showed me what it is I want.
那你说说  你想要什么
And what's that, huh? Huh? Huh?
我想要赢
I wanna win this.
那你也知道  拳场上你得先打赢我  对吧
You know you're gonna have to get through me, right?
我们又不是合作取胜
I'm not your damn sidekick, boo!
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
但谁打得赢谁还说不定呢
Maybe it's you who's gonna have to get through me!
好啊  亲爱的
Alright, honey.
干嘛呢  把实力都留到锦标赛上去好吗
Oh, hey! Save the full contact for the tournament!
对不起  教练  我的错
That was my bad, Coach.
事实证明  我不擅长看对手的进攻信号
Apparently, I'm really bad at reading signals.
是的  但也没必要把她往死里揍
Yeah, well, bromancing her to death isn't working.
继续练习
Keep moving!
开始吧
There you go.
诺拉  你在哪呢
Nora! Where you at?
我在这儿  教练
Over here, Coach!
今天表现不错  孩子
Hey, good job today, kid.
谢谢
Thanks.
感觉你终于开窍了  如鱼得水
I feel like your headspace is finally getting dialed in.
你需要的就是保持好这种状态
That's what you need, alright?
好了 今晚回家以后  好好休息
Now, I want you to go home tonight, get plenty of rest,
多吃点碳水化合物  多睡一会儿  好吗
load up on carbs, and get a lot of sleep. Alright?
然后拜托你把这头头发编成辫子
And please get that damn hair braided.
我原本就想把它随便弄一下  做个发髻
I was just gonna like, put it in like a bun or something.
别那样弄  我和他们说好了  直接去就行
No you're not. I got you covered, they're expecting you.
-今晚吗  -对
- Tonight? - Yep.
罗辛  我付不起这个钱
Rosheen, I don't have money to pay for this.
没事  不要操心钱的事  我已经搞定了
I got ya. It's taken care of, don't worry about it.
真的吗
Really?
谢谢您
Thank you.
当然  不能让我的布娃娃蓬头垢面就上场
Alright. My little rag doll won't be so raggy!
快去吧  孩子
Go get 'em, girl!
你好  需要做头发吗
Hi. Can I help you?
罗辛让我来  为我明天的比赛做头发
Um, Rosheen sent me to get my hair done for my fight.
比如  弄成辫子或者其他的什么
Like, braids or something?
我知道了  那我只收你两百美元
Yeah, yeah. I know. I can get you for two hundred dollars.
可罗辛说的是  "已经和你们说好了"
Oh. Rosheen said that it was "taken care of?"
你觉得我们这儿是什么店
What do you think this is?
给邋遢的白人女孩免费做头发的慈善机构
A charity for some straggedy-ass white girl?
抱歉  可能是有什么误会
I'm sorry there must have been some misunderstanding.
非常抱歉
I'm sorry.
哦  不  不  不  不  回来回来
Oh, no, no, no, no, come back, come back!
刚刚是在逗你玩  好吧  开玩笑的
I'm just teasing you! Come on, I'm playing!
快回来  现如今  大家也真是的
Come on in. Now, damn!
觉得所有人都是在针对自己  快来吧
Don't take everything so damn personal! Come on!
每句话都是在跟人说"对不起"
It's like every other word was "oh, sorry!"
到时候她就像定时炸弹那样
Like a ticking time bomb.
她一过来就把我这小店炸平了
She was gonna come back and shoot this whole place up.
你们别笑了  好了  想想
Y'all, stop! Okay, look.
我要
I am going to--
没事  没事  我会帮你
It's okay, it's okay. I'mma--
到时候  你看上去就是耀眼夺目的冠军
You know, I'mma make you look like a champion!
-拳击场上女孩比男的打得都狠  -这样吗
- Oh, yeah! Girls fight like, way harder than guys! - What?
对  就比如  男人上场打拳  打完会握手
Yeah, like, guys can go in, and they'll shake hands afterwards,
就很酷  但是有时候  女子拳击手就会
and they're all cool but girls, sometimes,
相互怀恨在心  让人厌恶
they hold a grudge. It's pretty nasty.
我能懂这种感觉
Mhm. I know that's right.
冠军小姐  闪亮登场
Well, Miss Champion. Viola!
快看呐
Look at you!
喜欢吗
You like it?
抱歉迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我得替那个被解雇的婊子顶班
I had to cover a shift for this bitch that got fired.
不用担心  没关系  不过看起来也不早了
Oh, no worries, it's fine. Look like it's getting late anyway.
除了你们几个"常客"  也没别人
Nobody here but the usual suspects.
对了  还有我们的女版"洛基"
Oh, and the "female Rocky" over here!
我身上没带钱  不然我定会给你小费的
Um, hey look, I would tip you if I had any money,
而且我最近还丢了工作
but I just lost my job.
没关系的
It's okay.
再说了  这些钱罗辛都帮你包了
And besides, Rosheen got you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
怎么一回事
What's going on?
这就是那个跟她妈妈一起住的疯婊子
That's that crazy ass bitch with the mother.
-天呐  -没想到吧
- Oh! - Yeah!
你刚刚他妈的说什么
The fuck did you just say?
婊子  你听得一清二楚了  好吗
Bitch, you heard what I said, okay?
所以赶紧给我滚出去  好吗
So take ya little ass outta here, alright?
平时什么也不干  现在想干什么
You not gon' do nothin'. You 'bout to do somethin'?
你想干什么吗
You gon' do somethin'?
我想你也不敢
That's what I thought.
站起来
Get up.
-好了  你给我出去  -好的  好的  好的
- Oh no, you gotta go. - Alright, alright, alright.
-不准在我的地盘上打架  -抱歉  抱歉
- You do not fight in my place! - I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
萨沙  你要干什
Sasha, what are you doi--
你好  你好  打扰一下  警官  警官
Hey, hey! Excuse me, Officer. Officer!
-怎么了  -我现在能打个电话吗
- What? - Can I get my phone call now, please?
我想找个人过来
I need to call someone.
是需要急救吗
Some type of medical emergency?
对的  我想找个医生过来检查下我的手
It is, actually. I need to see someone about my hand.
我觉得我的手好像是骨折了
I think I might have broke it.
先生  先生  她在撒谎
Sir! Sir, sir. She lyin'.
她向来谎话连篇  她才不需要什么急救
She always be lyin'. She ain't got no medical emergency.
我没有撒谎  你看我的手可能折了  拜托
I'm not lying! You can see that I might have broke my hand. Please.
看起来没那么糟
Doesn't look that bad.
你在说笑吗  我明天还有正事要做
Are you serious? I have a job tomorrow!
非常重要的正事
This is a very important job
大概几个小时以后我就得赶过去  好吗
that I need to get to, like, in a few hours, okay?
-她在说谎  -拜托你了
- She lyin'. - Please!
她在撒谎  怕是她的"小妹妹"才有急症
She lyin.' Her coochie is the only thing
急着去见人  懂了吗
that got a medical emergency, okay?
妇科医生怕是要用扣绳
The gynecologist gon' need a chin strap
绑在她两腿之间才能治好  懂了吗
to deal with that offense between her legs, okay?
这个笑话不错  待会我和警长讲讲
That's good! I'm gonna tell the Captain about that one.
听到了吗  诺拉  他们以后就会讲起
You hear that, Nora? He's gonna tell 'em about
你腿间的罪行了  臭婊子
your offence between your legs, bitch!
我是真不敢相信你居然找上门来
Man, I can't believe that you came to my work
还对我动手动脚  婊子
and laid your hands on me, bitch.
你要付出代价  我和你没完  听到了吗
You are going to pay! This is not over, you hear me?
全都怪你
This is on you!
对啊  你怎么不
Yeah. Why don't you
你为什么不打电话给你那些
Why don't you go call one yo lil'
开着奔驰  宝马的
Benz-drivin', BMW-havin',
有钱有势的金主嫖客呢
bougie-ass hooker workers now, huh?
给他们打电话啊  打啊  打给他们
Call 'em for that! Call! Call 'em!
求他们把你保释出去
Tell 'em to bail you outta jail,
看看他们来得能有多快
see how fast they come!
你好  警官
Uh, hey, Officer!
你好  拜托您过来一下
Hey! Hey! Please come here.
我能否用一下我的手机
Am I allowed to use, uh, like my cell phone
找一个号码
to get a number out of my phone
然后我打一个电话
so that I can make my phone call?
不行
No.
-拜托  -不行
- Please? - No.
我记不太清他的号码
I don't know his number by heart.
但我就打这一个电话  就一个  我保证
That's- that'd be my one phone call and that'll be it, I promise!
该死的  诺拉
Goddamn, Nora!
你能不能有点尊严
Have some respect for yourself.
活得体面些
Some decency!
你真的要给那些男人们打电话
You really gon' call one of them Johns
用他们的臭钱  把你保释出去吗
who be droppin' nickels in you?
他不是
He's not a J-- Uh.
他是我朋友  拜托了  我只是记不清号码
It's a friend of mine. Please, I just don't know his number.
你哪来的朋友  能不能说句真话听听
You ain't got no friends. Stop lyin'.
你不要再撒谎了  我们都在牢里蹲着呢
You ain't got to lie now! We here together, we in jail!
听着  拜托
Look, please?
拜托
Please?
听着  我看看我能做什么  好吗
Look, I'll see what I can do, alright?
你也能为我做些什么吗  爱笑的麦吉警官
Can you see what you can do for me, too? Laugh McGee?
给你  你要的号码
Here's your numbers.
用我们的电话打  按9可以拨外线
Use our phone, dial nine for an outside line.
谢谢您
Thank you.
就是  就是打个电话给他  没事的
Just call-- Just call him. It's fine.
你好  我是杰森  这是我的电话
Hi! You've reached Jason, and this is my phone!
非常感谢你的来电
Thank you so much for calling me.
希望你最近过的顺心如意
I hope you are doing something wonderful with your days,
我知道你正着手大事
and I know you are accomplishing something great!
请留言
Please leave a message,
我一定会尽快给你回复的
and I will surely get back to you as soon as I can!
你好  杰森  很抱歉这么晚打电话给你
Hey, uh, Jason. It's um-- I'm so sorry for calling you so late, um.
或者说  抱歉这么早打给你  我是诺拉
Or so early. I'm not, um-- But, uh, this is Nora.
我们是那天在药房认识的
Um, we met at the pharmacy.
你也来我工作的地方找过我
Um, and you also came to my work.
所以  我打给你是因为  我遇到了点麻烦
so uh, I needed to call, um, I'm in a little bit of a-- of a jam.
你记得我跟你说过的拳击锦标赛吗
Um. You know that fight tournament that I- I had told you about?
我们的红发女子真幸运  有人保释你出去
Luck of the redheads. Someone's posted bail.
告诉他  谢谢
Tell him never mind.
我不能再欠别人人情了
I can't be owin' anybody like that again.
好的  红发妹  我会转达的  只是说
OKay, Red. You got it. It's just that--
哇  听听  他们现在都给你取了个爱称呢
Oh, look! They makin' up nicknames for you here now.
去吧  红发妹
Here you go, Red.
我们有钱的"赎妓"队长来了
Rich ass Captain Save-A-Ho is here!
保释你的不是什么有钱男人
If it makes any difference,
如果告诉你  你会好受些的话
it's not some rich ass guy.
这么些年来  她一拿到现金就往枕套里藏
She's been shoveling all that cash in her pillowcase for years.
玛丽
Mary,
谢谢你
thank you.
另一只手
Let's go.
诺拉  我怎么告诫你的
Nora, what the hell do I say about
私人恩怨不要影响到我们的比赛
taking this shit outside the gym?
我知道  这样真的很蠢
I know, it was really stupid.
但我发誓  没看上去那么糟
But it's not that bad, I swear.
会好起来的
It's gonna be fine.
其他都还好吧
Everything else okay?
其他都很好  只是说
Yeah. Everything else is fine, yeah.
只是伤到了指关节
It's just this, it's just the knuckles.
也许你今天不应该上场了
Maybe you shouldn't do this today.
求你了  罗辛 我必须这么做
Please, Rosheen, I have to do this.
我别无选择  我今天一定要上场
I don't have a choice. I have to fight today.
真的没那么糟  我发誓
It's really not that bad, I swear.
拜托了
Please.
我逗你玩的
I'm messin' with you.
我会阻止你参赛吗
Me, stop you from fightin'?
恐怕还没等我插手  他们就会把我
They'd take my old ass out in the back alley
拖出后门暴打一顿  是不是
before that'd happen, right?
那我倒不知道  不过我可能会被揍得很惨
I don't know about that. I'd probably get my ass kicked.
没人能百分之百投入战斗的
Hey, nobody is ever a hundred percent goin' into a fight.
人们总会碰到些
You're always gonna have a little somethin'
十分棘手的倒霉事
that's really fucked up.
挺过去就好了  对吗
You just gotta fight through it, right?
好啦
Okay.
来  把手分开
Give it. Spread 'em.
综合格斗大学
从这里开始
观众朋友们  看起来阿依莎情况
Ladies and gentlemen, it doesn't look good
不太乐观  她被压在了下面
for Aisha. She's on the bottom.
不  不  她翻过来了
No, no, she's turned it around,
她翻到了上面  重新掌握优势
she's on the top! She's dominating!
她们重新站起来了  她们站起来了
They're back on their feet, they're back on their feet.
好的  我们将看到一些
Alright, we're goin' in for some
漂亮的泰拳对抗了
good Muay Thai exchanges here!
踢得好  阿依莎踢得好
Good kick, good kick by Aisha!
结束战斗  阿依莎把她拿下了
And it is over! Aisha knocked her out!
诺拉·费利克斯和蔡斯·亚历山大
Nora Felix and Chase Alexander?
你们俩下一组  五分钟准备
You two are next. Five minutes.
来和我对打啊  来格斗啊
Kumite! Kumite!
很好
Great.
一  二
One, two!
我晋级下一轮了  诺拉
On to the next motherfuckin' round, Nora!
你什么时候上场
When are you goin' up?
-下一组  -好啊
- Next. - Okay.
祝你好运  快去吧  快去
Well, good luck. Go get 'em. Go get 'em.
你是一个战士  这就是你来此的原因
You're a fighter. That's why you're here.
这就是你为何在战斗  以及你为何
That's why you're fightin' and why you can fight
能与你所经历的一切抗争
all those things you're goin' through.
某些东西将你带来这里
Something got you here!
无论是某个原因  还是
Whether it was a reason or something--
还是你正在经历的什么
something that you're going through--
正是它让你来到这里
that's what brought you here
而现在是你释放的时候
and it's bringin' that out of you.
你需要把它释放出来
You've gotta let it.
诺拉
Nora.
妈妈
Mom?
蔡斯超人般的一击
Nice Superman punch by Chase!
诺拉似乎陷入困境
Nora looks like she's in trouble!
天啊  诺拉好像不行了
Oh, man, it looks like Nora's in trouble.
她必须做点什么  她必须得起来
She's gotta do something. She's gotta get up!
肋骨上两脚踢得不错
Two good kicks to the ribs.
诺拉重新掌控了局面
Nora's comin' back.
天啊  来吧
Oh, man! There we go!
诺拉把她逼到笼壁了  锁死她
Nora's got her up against the cage. Utilizing that clench!
膝盖踢得很猛  我觉得她不行了
Throwing really good knees. I think she's in trouble--
蔡斯要不行了
Chase might be in trouble!
蔡斯插眼犯规
We got an eye gauge by Chase!
快分开  快分开  快分开  快分开
Break it up, break it up, break it up, break it up!
-住手  -你们是来参赛的
- Come on! - We're here to win a contest,
不是互相伤害的  走吧
not hurt each other! Now let's go!
我们曾一起经历过磨难  没人能伤害你了
The hell we've been through, no one can hurt you.
-彼得斯太太到了吗  -还没有
- Is Ms. Peters here yet? - No, not yet.
不过她会来的  别等她了  宝贝
But she will be. Don't wait for her, honey.
快走吧  走吧  走吧
Just go! Go, go, go!
好吧  但我不想让你一个人待着
Yeah, but I don't wanna leave you alone.
我没事的  来抱一下
I'll be fine. Now give me a hug.
好的
Okay.
我可能要躺一会儿
I might lie down for a bit, anyway.
你还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
好着呢
I'm fine!
去大干一场吧
You go kick ass!
我爱你  宝宝
I love you, kiddo.
我也爱你  妈妈
I love you, too, Mom.
我怎么样
How'm I doing?
糟糕得要命  但你赢定了
Fuckin' horrible. But you're winnin'.
真的吗
Really?
你身处对抗中可能不觉得
It's hard to see while you're in a fight,
但大家都看出来了
but everyone else can see it.
现在回去  去把她拿下
Now get in there and kick her ass.
双手时刻防卫  双脚不停移动
You keep those hands up, you keep movin'.
记住了吗  吐出来
Alright? Spit it out.
很好  上场吧  完胜她  加油
There you go. Alright. Let's go. Own it! C'mon!
诺拉  你不可能每件事都要斗到底
Nora, you can't fight your way through everything.
是啊  妈妈  也不是我要斗的
Yeah, well, it's not like I'm trying to fight, Mom.
我的生活就是这样的
It's just the way my life works.
诺拉
Nora.
妈妈  我要照顾你  对吧
Mom, I take care of you, don't I?
对
Yes.
我还要确保你不会独自待太长时间
And I make sure that you're not alone for too long.
我每晚回家都要保证桌上有吃的
And I make sure that I have food on the table every night
保证你能吃上晚饭
when I get home. For you.
我还得确保你有药吃
And I make sure that I have your medicine.
甚至保证你喝得上威士忌
And I make sure that you have your scotch.
玩得上填字游戏  对吧
And your crossword puzzles. Right?
我就不明白了  你为什么总在质疑
So I don't understand. Why do you keep questioning me
我在做什么
on what I'm trying to do?
还有我怎么生活
And how I'm living my life?
我已经尽力了
You know, I'm trying my best!
这是我能做的最好的了
This is the best I can do.
这一切都不是白来的
No, one's giving me these things.
我爱你  这还不够吗
I love you! Is that not enough?
这对我永远是最满足的
It's always been enough.
你不停地奋斗
You fight and fight.
做得不错  就像我当初一样
You're good at it. Like I was.
但是  有些事情你只能接受
But, there are just certain things you're gonna need to accept.
-我没法和你说了  这是  -诺拉
- I can't talk to you. This is-- - Nora!
我费了这么大劲  图什么
Came all this way. For what?
没关系的
It's okay--
有关系  一点都不好
It's not okay. It's not okay, guys!
好了  你状态还不错
Alright, it's not too bad.
可以继续下一场比赛
You're in good shape for your next fight.
等等  我赢了吗
Wait, I won?
你再问我就不让你参赛了
You keep talkin' like this and I will stop the next fight.
不  等等  罗辛  我很抱歉
No, wait, Rosheen. I'm sorry.
我  我很好
I'm-- Yeah, I'm, I'm good.
好啦  我开玩笑的  你当然没问题
Alright. I'm kiddin'. You're there.
给  咱们走  孩子你没问题的
Here. Let's go. You got this, kid.
呼吸
Breathe.
我的小诺拉
My little Nora.
都长成大姑娘了
All grown up.
可我还是能把你抱住
But you still fit into my arms.
你还记从前咱们也这样睡  那时你爸爸还
Do you remember sleeping like this when your father...
咱俩都像小宝宝一样  缩成一小团
We were both just babies. All curled up into a little ball.
是啊  我记得
Yeah, I remember.
你暖暖的
You were so warm.
小头发轻挠着我的鼻子
And your hair tickled my nose.
你就是我的小天使
You were my little angel.
是你挽救了我的一生
You saved my life back then.
我挽救你了吗
I saved?
当你爸再也受不了我的暴脾气时
When your father couldn't hack it with my ornery ass anymore,
你成为我生活唯一的动力
you were the only thing that kept me going.
你是我每天早上起床
You were the only reason I had
继续生活下去的唯一理由
to get up every morning and carry on.
因为我得照顾你
Because I had to take care of you.
所以说
So,
我明白你现在为我做的一切  我真的明白
I understand what you're doing for me right now. I really do.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom--
妈妈
Mom,
这是我应该做的事  我并不引以为傲
I'm not proud of what I had to do--
你爸常说
Your father used to say
"女人啊  都是头发长见识短"
"A woman sees the world the way the woman sees it."
他一这样  我就知道他喝多了
And that way, I would know that he was drunk,
我会揍他脖子
and I would punch him in the goddamn neck.
是啊  这场面可不是每个小孩
Yeah. Fun scene for a child
都能看到的  我当然记得
to grow up in. I remember.
这也让你变得坚强
Well, certainly toughened you up.
-人世多艰  -没错
- It's a tough world. - Yeah.
人世多艰
It's a tough world.
厨房的墙上现在还留着个凹痕
I think there's still a dent in the wall in the kitchen
就是你当时扔他时留下的
from when you threw him.
我先伤害他  他才不会伤害我
Well, I had to hurt him so that he didn't hurt me first.
可到头来  他还是伤害了我
And in the end, he still did.
有时候  我真希望自己当初
Sometimes, I wish I could have stepped
能从他的角度想想
into his shoes back then.
那样我就知道他的处境有多糟糕了
'Cause I would have seen how messed up he was,
那样我就会选择离开
and I would have walked out that door,
抱着你一起离开
holding you in my arms.
也许生活是场战斗  诺拉
Life is a fight, maybe, Nora.
但你不必伤害周围的每一个人
But you don't have to hurt everyone around you.
你径自走开就好了
You can just walk away.
因为人生不止一条道路
'Cause there, there are other ways to win.
你是一个美丽而坚强的女人
You are a beautiful, strong woman.
我真为你骄傲
And I am so proud of you.
我要是离去了  肯定会非常想你的
And I'm gonna miss you so goddamn much when I go.
裁判就没看到吗
How the hell'd the judges not see me
我揍了你整整三轮
whoop your ass for three rounds?
我把你打得落花流水
I had your ass, bitch!
而且你很明白  这场是我的比赛
And you know it! This was my fight!
-你他妈的在这里做了手脚  -别吵了
- You fuckin' rigged somethin' around here - Hey!
简  出去  都结束了
Jane, get the hell out of here! It's over!
赶紧走
Get outta here!
我们又赢了吗
We won again?
你打得真挺辛苦的
You're in one hell of a zone.
是啊
Yeah.
不过有几击很不错
But you took a few good shots.
来  我给你处理下伤口
Here, lemme close some of those cuts up.
坐过来  把头仰过去
Here, put your head back.
稍等
Hold on.
好了  仰着别动
Alright, hold it still.
我给你处理下  可别再裂开了
Lemme get this; I don't want it to split back open.
最后一场
One more fight.
没事  罗辛
We good, Rosheen.
反正我永远挺我媳妇
Always got my girl's corner, anyway.
是吗
Is that right?
罗辛  没事  她也没人可以依靠
Rosheen, we good. She doesn't have anybody, anyway.
-不能再对了  -亲爱的  友好点
- Damn right. - Babe. Be nice, man.
如果我打输了
If I was gonna lose to anybody,
阿依莎  那一定是输给你
it'd be you, Aisha.
阿依莎  她忽悠你呢
Aisha, she's trying to get into your head.
别理她
Don't listen to her.
你还能再继续吗
Are you okay to go on?
罗辛  我说过了  我不能退出  我得
Rosheen, I told you, I cannot quit. I gotta--
我逗你玩呢
I'm messin' with you!
你一点也没有放弃的意思
There ain't an ounce of quit in you.
可阿依莎的实力多强你一清二楚
But you know damn good and well Aisha can knock people out.
她没准会把你胳膊扯下来
Or she can rip your arm out.
你必须要专心  保持精神集中
I need you to focus and stay focused,
真搞不懂你今天到底在想什么
'cause I don't know where the hell your head's at today.
这一天都怪怪的
It's been a weird day.
我们曾一起经历过磨难  没人能伤害你了
The hell we've been through, no one can hurt you.
-彼得斯来了吗太太  -还没有
- Is Ms. Peters here yet? - No, not yet.
别等她了  宝贝  快走吧
But don't wait for her, honey. Just, just go!
走吧  走吧
Go, go, go!
妈妈  我不想留你独自待着
Mom, I don't wanna leave you alone.
我没事的  来抱一下  亲一个
I will be fine. Now you give me a hug and a kiss.
我可能要躺一会儿
I may lay down for a bit.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好得很  也骄傲得很
Yep! Just a proud mama!
去大干一场吧
You go kick ass!
我爱你  宝宝
I love you, kiddo.
我也爱你  妈妈
I love you, too, Ma.
好的  她们来到了赛场中央
Alright, the two are at center.
能感受到她们之间的紧张气氛
You can see the tension in their--
-没错  -教练之间也是
- Yeah. - Between their coaches.
阿依莎已经准备好  随时出击
Aisha looks ready to go. She looks ready to pounce.
-诺拉看起来很放松  -是的
- Nora looks-- Relaxed. - Yeah.
-好的  互碰一下拳套  -准备开战
- Alright, touch gloves. - Gettin' ready to break,
互碰拳套  开始
touchin' gloves, and here we go!
等下  伙计们  不  等等  有事要发生
Wait, guys! No, wait, something's happening!
对  是有事  有比赛呢  快去迎战
Yeah, it is! A fight! Now, get out there and fight!
加油  诺拉  把手举起来  加油
C'mon, Nora! Get your hands up! C'mon!
该死
Oh shit.
tap out：快速拍击地面或对手身躯三次表示认输
诺拉可能随时会拍垫认输  她有点
Nora could be tappin' out any second. She's kind of...
她要认输了
She's gonna tap!
加油  诺拉  摆脱掉她  翻身挣脱
C'mon, Nora, get out of her! Roll out!
-她有点  -她不行了  要认输了
- She's kind of... - She's gonna tap, she's gonna tap!
加油  诺拉  翻身挣脱  翻身挣脱
C'mon, Nora! Roll out of it! Roll out of it!
好一个反败为胜
What a reversal!
就这样  漂亮  好极了 太棒了
There you go! Yes! Yes! Yes!
她竟然翻过来了
She's got her back turned again!
你在干什么  快离开那
What are you doing? Get out there!
上啊
Come on now!
转过身去
Turn around!
诺拉  别这样
Nora, don't!
冲上去  打败她  打败她
Get out there! Go get her! Go get her!
-她冲上去了  -这就是当前赛况
- There it is. - That's what's happening right now.
防守啊  抬起胳膊
Protect yourself! Get your arms up!
振作点  挺住  诺拉  你要反击
No, come on! Come on, Nora, you gotta fight!
这就是你想要的  这就是你梦寐以求的
This what you want? This what you really want?
加把劲  注意你的肩膀  别受伤
Come on! Watch your shoulder! No!
加油  加油
Come on! Come on!
诺拉  快挣脱
Nora, get outta that!
诺拉  认输吧
Nora, tap!
她必须得做点什么了
She's gotta do something.
如果她什么都不做  就胜负分明了
If she doesn't do anything, this fight is over.
认输吧
Come on!
-她的肩膀  感觉快脱臼了  -右臂
- Her shoulder. It's about ready to go. - That right arm.
那只右臂  她会认输吗
That right arm. Is she gonna tap?
我的天啊  一方选手手臂脱臼了
Oh my God! The arm snapped!
完蛋了
Aw, shit!
如果裁判认为这回合已经变成"一边倒"
或者在比赛进行中一方拳手严重受伤，将会停止比赛
裁判会叫停比赛吗  她的手臂受伤了
Are the refs gonna do anything? Her arm!
她还在拳台上  裁判会终止比赛吗
She's still in the fight! Is the ref gonna stop this?
-他应该会  -我不知道他会不会
- He should. - I don't know if he's going to.
你为什么不终止比赛
Why didn't you stop it?
她没有拍垫认输
She didn't tap.
裁判  她没有认输  她没有拍垫认输
Ref, she didn't tap out! She didn't tap out!
-她确实没有  -终止比赛  快终止
- She didn't tap. - Stop it! Stop it!
你还能行吗  比赛  继续
You good? Fight! Let's go.
好了宝贝  上吧  赶紧赢了这场比赛
Aight, baby, c'mon! Finish this off! Right now!
我该怎么做
What do I do?
赢了比赛  赢了她
Finish it off, finish her off!
她无力还击了  上吧  宝贝  赢了她
She's there for the taking, baby! C'mon, go get her!
裁判  结束比赛  你愣着干嘛
Ref, stop it! What are you doing?
终止比赛
What are you doing?
诺拉  你最好停下
Nora, you better stop.
离开拳台  诺拉
Get outta here, Nora.
诺拉  别硬撑了
Nora, get the fuck out of here.
我认为裁判应该叫停这场比赛
I think the ref should stop this fight.
她已经没法进攻了  连防守都没有
She's not even playing, not defense.
又是针对手臂的招式
Arm, again.
这次是另一边
There is the other...
她会认输吗
Is she gonna tap?
保持呼吸  保持呼吸  孩子  保持呼吸
Keep breathing, keep breathing, kid! Keep breathing!
加把劲  诺拉  翻身挣脱  翻身挣脱
C'mon Nora! Roll out of it, roll out of it!
好样的  就这样  太棒了
Atta girl, atta girl! Woo! Yes!
占据上位  膝盖  伤她的膝盖
Get on top! Get her knee, take her knees!
控制住她的膝盖  诺拉
Take her knee, Nora!
对  就这样  就这样  好极了
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
好吧  我的天啊  局势再次反转
Okay, alright. Oh my God, the tables have turned here!
阿依莎的膝盖现在被诺拉紧紧锁住
So now, Nora has Aisha in a really tight knee lock.
-是的  阿依莎有麻烦了  真是  -就这样
- Yeah, Aisha's in trouble, now. This is... - Yes!
这招会一锤定音吗
Is this gonna take the fight?
她伤成这样居然还能继续比赛
I couldn't believe she's still going.
真是一场难得一见的比拼
I have not seen a fight like this in years!
加油宝贝  挺住  翻身挣脱出来
C'mon, baby! C'mon! Get out, get out!
挣脱出来  翻身
Get out, roll over!
天呐  太不可思议了
Come on. This is incredible!
诺拉仍然控制着对手  这简直
Nora's still got her. There's...
铃响得很及时
Saved by the bell.
精彩的第一回合  难以置信
That was an incredible first round. Unbelievable.
感觉诺拉从一开始就拼命了
It looked like Nora was done from the get-go.
像是全然不顾了
Like completely out of it,
面对强势的对手  从下位顽强翻身
turning to her corner, turning her back.
-这两位选手身体素质都很好  -是的
- A massive amount of heart on both girls, here. - Yeah.
真是一场激烈的缠斗
What a fight!
但我觉得  两位选手都缺少防守
But lack of D, on both, I would say.
是  我也这么觉得
Yeah, I would say so.
-进攻较多  防守较少  -对
- There's a lot of offense, not a lot of defense. - Yeah.
还有几个压制性动作
Almost a couple submissions.
应该在防守上再下点功夫
Work on the defense a bit.
上一场能赢很不容易了  孩子
Way to survive that round, kid.
现在医生要把你的手臂归位  好吗
Now, he's gonna have to pop it in now, okay?
好吧  深吸一口气
Alright. Take a deep breath.
你能行的  看着我  来吧
You got it. Look at me. C'mon.
放松  放松  保持呼吸  呼吸
Relax, relax. Breathe, breathe, breathe!
好的  就这儿
Okay, right here.
-该死  -你很棒
- Oh, shit! - You're good!
-归位了吗  -好的
- Is it in? - Okay, okay.
我坚持不下去了  我撑不住了
I can't keep doing this. I can't keep going.
没关系  诺拉  没事的  这不是问题
That's okay, Nora. It's okay. It's not a problem.
上一回合确实很艰险
That was a hell of a fight!
不  不  你不明白
No, no, you don't understand.
我觉得我妈妈  她可能要自杀
I think my mom, she's gonna commit suicide.
诺拉  你  你妈妈已经去世了
Nora, you... your mom's gone.
你怎么知道的  什么时候的事
How did you know? When did you find out? Wha...?
亲爱的  她两个月前就去世了
Honey, she passed away two months ago.
不  不  不可能  怎么可能  不会的
No! No, that's not... No! No, no, no, no!
不会的  那是不可能的
That's not, that's not possible!
我还参加了葬礼  记得吗
Hey, hey, hey. I was at the funeral, remember?
还有  你的脚被玻璃扎伤了
And... Yeah, and it took like, over a month for your...
过了一个多月才好  你记得吗
for your feet to heal from the glass cuts, you remember?
不  不  这不可能
No! No, this can't be right!
深呼吸
Take a deep breath!
-你能行的  -放轻松
- You got it. - Take it easy.
玛丽
Mary...
谢谢你
Thank you.
我才见过她啊  今天早上还见了
I just saw her! I just saw her this morning!
你们搞错了吧  不是你们说的那样
I... You guys, this isn't right! No!
你还好吗
You feeling okay?
我也爱你  妈妈
I love you too, Mom.
我挽救了你吗
I saved?
这是我应该做的事  我并不引以为傲
I'm not proud of what I had to do.
就算你要打我  我也得让你清醒过来
You're gonna kick my ass, but I'm gonna stop this.
不  不  不用  拜托  我能继续比赛
No, no, no, please! Don't do that! Please! I can do this!
听着  我知道你是对的
Look, I know you're right!
那是两个月前的事了
You... It was two months ago.
我知道  那是两个月前的事了
I remember, it was two months ago.
我能行的
I can do this.
我要为了她赢了这场比赛  我必须这么做
I'm gonna do it for her. I have to finish. I have to!
诺拉  如果你想退出比赛也没关系的
Nora, it's okay. We're just gonna walk away.
我必须这么做  既是为她
I gotta do this. I gotta do this for her.
也是为了我自己  我必须这么做
I gotta do this for me. I gotta do this!
加油
C'mon.
准备好了吗  好的
You ready? Okay.
不行  不行  我不行  我做不到
I can't, I can't! I can't. I can't do this.
站起来  你可以的
C'mon! C'mon.
-好了  起来  -我不行  我做不到
- Okay, get up. - I can't. I can't.
准备好了吗  还能继续比赛吗
What are you gonna do here? Are you okay to continue?
请稍等  谢谢
One second, please. Thank you.
我听不清你说话
I can't hear you.
我听不清
Can't hear you.
妈妈  我听不见你说的
Mom, I can't hear you.
我听不清
I can't hear you.
我们退出比赛
I'm gonna stop the fight.
-不  不要  拜托  不要  -没关系的
- No! Please! No, no, no, no! Please, no! - Come on.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
为什么会这样
妈妈  我该怎么做
Mom, what do I do?
我该怎么做
What do I do?
去他妈的
Fuck it!
没关系
It's okay.
不  去他妈的
No, fuck it!
你自己之前说
You know, you said
比赛之前永远不可能百分之百准备好
that you never go into a fight one hundred percent,
也不可能总是以最好的状态面对生活
and you said that you never face life at one hundred percent
因为总会有扯淡的事发生  对吧  你说的
because it's all just bullshit, right? You said that!
我说过  你确定要继续吗
I said that. Are you sure you wanna do this?
不确定
No.
这太蠢了
This is stupid!
妈的
Fuck!
我唬你呢
I'm fuckin' with you!
好吧  她好了  我们参加下一轮
Yeah, she's good! We're in.
我们回来了  好了  好了
We're back! Alright. Alright.
另外  你也不想让你的铁杆粉丝失望吧
Plus, you don't wanna let down your super fan over there.
诺拉  诺拉  诺拉  诺拉
Nora! No-ra! No-ra! No-ra! No-ra!
诺拉最棒
诺拉
No-ra!
-来吧  冠军  我们上  -诺拉  诺拉
- Come on, champ. Let's go. - No-ra! No-ra!
让我们回到这场比赛的第二轮  但是
And we're back for the second round of this fight here, but...
-什么情况  -他妈的  结束了吗
- What? - Fuck you, it's over?
等等  发生了什么  什么叫比赛结束了
Wait, wait, what happened? What do you mean the fight's over?
乱搞什么  怎么回事
Bullshit! What the fuck?
-我很好  -裁判  我说过  她好着呢
- I'm good! - Man, I told you she was good!
她可不会退出
She didn't come out of this...
裁判在挥舞他的手  等下
Woah! The ref! He's wavin' his hands! Hold on!
红方退出了  是红方
Woah, woah, red corner quit. Red corner quit!
裁判宣布红方退出了比赛
The judge is yelling red corner has withdrawn.
试着动一下这里  好了
Let's try here. Alright.
我没事
I'm okay.
我们得让她离开这
We need to get her out of here.
她努力都白费了
She worked too hard for this.
不行  不  不能这样
No. No, no, no, no.
你不能把冠军拱手让人
You can't give this to me.
我没有  我也做不到  我膝盖受伤了
I didn't. I can't. It's my knee.
我失败了
I'm fucked up.
我不会让你就这样放弃的
I'm not gonna let you just quit, then.
我没有放弃
I didn't quit.
我下次会赢
I'll win next time.
但这次你赢了  赢得很彻底
But you won. This was all you.
用你自己的一套就他妈赢了
Got a weird way to fuckin' do it.
但确实是你赢了
But this was all you.
靠近点
C'mere.
我够不到你
I can't get to you.
我爱你
I love you.
好吧  看起来红方已经退出了
Well, it looks like the red corner has withdrawn.
这是官方的说法吗
Is that the official word?
这样的话诺拉  诺拉赢了
And it looks like Nora... Nora has won.
这是属于你的时刻  好好享受吧
This is your moment. Fuckin' take that shit in.
这场比赛  真是令人难以置信  诺拉
This fight, unbelievable. Nora!
祝贺这位新生冠军
Congratulations to the new champ!
疯狂的回归
Crazy comeback, wow!
令人难忘的夜晚
Wow, what an evening.
是啊  我真不敢相信她赢了
Yeah I can't believe that just happened!
这才是我的姑娘
That's my girl!
你知道吗
You know what?
从你来到训练馆  一直以来的努力训练
You showed up, you worked hard,
今天终于成功了
you did it.
诺拉  诺拉
No-ra! No-ra!
是我们成功了
We did it.
是你自己刻苦训练  亲爱的
You did all the hard work, sweetheart.
我只是不停在旁边嚷嚷
I just did a lot of yellin'.
-对吧  -你确实很擅长"嚷嚷"
- Right? - You're good at yelling, that's for sure.
我知道我擅长
Hey, I know that's real.
你还好吧  冠军
You okay, champ?
嗯  我很好
Yeah, I'm all good.
♪ 再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ So give me one more day ♪
♪ 去寻找一条路线 ♪
♪ Give me one more way ♪
♪ 让我学会忍受痛苦 ♪
♪ I swear I can handle the pain ♪
♪ 即使你已不在身边 ♪
♪ Then you're free to walk away ♪
♪ 再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ Give me one more day ♪
♪ 去寻找一条路线 ♪
♪ Give me one more way ♪
♪ 让你感受我的痛苦 ♪
♪ To feel the pain I'm in ♪
♪ 即使你已远在天边 ♪
♪ Then you're free to walk away ♪
♪ 请再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ But give me one day ♪
♪ 在你离开之前 ♪
♪ Before you choose to fade away ♪